https://lifelinepilots.org/privacy-statement/

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.lifelinepilots.org and LifeLine Pilots and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to LifeLine Pilots include www.lifelinepilots.org and LLP. The LLP website is a non-profit site. By using the LLP website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
We do not collect personally identifiable information from our users. We may gather personal or non-personal information in the future. Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by LLP.
This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the LLP website.
LLP encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from LLP so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. LLP is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the LLP website.
Security of your Personal Information
LLP secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.
Children Under Thirteen
LLP does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Changes to this Statement
LLP will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. LLP encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how LLP is protecting your information.
Contact Information
LLP welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that LLP has not adhered to this Statement, please contact LLP at:
LifeLine Pilots
Byerly Terminal, Suite 302
6100 W. Dirksen Parkway
Peoria, Illinois 61607
Email Address:
missions@lifelinepilots.org
Telephone number:
1-800-822-7972
Effective as of January 01, 2013.
Board of Directors/StaffTestimonialsStay In TouchFast Facts Back
LifeLine BlogContact
× Close Panel
